<DOC>
<DOCID> fsh_29326 </DOCID>
<DOCTYPE SOURCE="telephone"> CONVERSATION </DOCTYPE>
<DATETIME> 20041205-17:13:56 </DATETIME>
<BODY>
<TEXT>
<TURN>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-8" start="451" end="461"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-9" start="461" end="465">Hi.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-10" start="465" end="482">Good evening.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-11" start="482" end="488"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-12" start="488" end="498">Hello.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-13" start="498" end="508"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-14" start="508" end="529">How&apos;re you doing?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-15" start="529" end="535"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-16" start="535" end="549">Good evening.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-17" start="549" end="589">My name is Jean, and I&apos;m in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Arizona</ENAMEX>.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-18" start="589" end="599"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-19" start="599" end="623">Oh, from <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Arizona</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-20" start="623" end="645">How are you doing?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-21" start="645" end="651"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-22" start="651" end="672">I&apos;m fine, thank you.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-23" start="672" end="697">And what&apos;s your name?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-24" start="697" end="707"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-26" start="755" end="761"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-27" start="761" end="794"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX>, calling from <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">New York</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-28" start="794" end="813">Glad to meet you.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-29" start="813" end="894">Well, the topic is
interesting, but they&apos;ve been having this one for three days.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-30" start="894" end="943">I don&apos;t
know why they&apos;re so obsessed with it.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-31" start="943" end="953"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-32" start="953" end="1046">Seems like it&apos;s a weekend,  or they want to get as much as they can
feedback from people.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-33" start="1046" end="1052"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-34" start="1052" end="1072">I guess so, Yes.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-35" start="1072" end="1082"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-36" start="1082" end="1115">And so what do you think was-</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-37" start="1115" end="1121"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
didn&apos;t watch the <Event TYPE="Justice" SUBTYPE="Trial-Hearing">trial</Event> at all.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-39" start="1223" end="1233"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-40" start="1233" end="1241">Mhm.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
to me much more important, but um.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-44" start="1626" end="1787">Perhaps it was because he seemed,
uh, a very human kind of person and, and you cou- you couldn&apos;t really
<sentence ID="SENT-47" start="1938" end="1950"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohamed</ENAMEX>?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-48" start="1950" end="1960"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-49" start="1960" end="1969">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-50" start="1969" end="1975"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-51" start="1975" end="2023">And what do you- What do you think about it?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-52" start="2023" end="2033"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
year almost, now.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-55" start="2257" end="2268">It was-</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-56" start="2268" end="2274"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-57" start="2274" end="2292">When you what?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-58" start="2292" end="2302"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-59" start="2302" end="2333">It was -- taking so much time.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-60" start="2333" end="2347">Long time.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-61" start="2347" end="2353"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-62" start="2353" end="2361">Yes.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-63" start="2361" end="2371"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-64" start="2371" end="2401">The case is almost one year.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-65" start="2401" end="2465">Like last,  uh, Christmas if I&apos;m not,
uh, recalling my memory.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-66" start="2465" end="2507">So for one year, it&apos;s really a good time.</sentence>
<sentence ID="SENT-67" start="2507" end="2559">Hu- So I&apos;m asking myself why it took such a long</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-68" start="2559" end="2565"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-69" start="2565" end="2572">Hm.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-70" start="2572" end="2582"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-71" start="2582" end="2709">It may be because -- it&apos;s quite important,  or so there is so many
everything&apos;s, I mean,  it&apos;s, it&apos;s a really different case.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-72" start="2709" end="2763">But,  the
quo- the nice quotient is about the media.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-73" start="2763" end="2801">But the media have biased
in this,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-74" start="2801" end="2807"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-75" start="2807" end="2815">Yes.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-76" start="2815" end="2825"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-77" start="2825" end="2834">or not?</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-78" start="2834" end="2948">I believe that media is a very good, uh,  I mean, uh,  way
the media,  you and I, how we will be knowing?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-80" start="3013" end="3019"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
favor</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-83" start="3101" end="3111"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-84" start="3111" end="3142">I- -- No, I don&apos;t think so.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-85" start="3142" end="3148"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-86" start="3148" end="3199">No, I didn&apos;t think so either from what I heard.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-87" start="3199" end="3209"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
but in this issue they were just -- covering what&apos;s happening,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-89" start="3348" end="3354"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-90" start="3354" end="3362">Yes.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-91" start="3362" end="3372"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-92" start="3372" end="3407">and, uh, they give us the picture.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-93" start="3407" end="3449">It was a camera -- to give you the
view.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-94" start="3449" end="3502">I don&apos;t think they were biased in this case here.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-95" start="3502" end="3508"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jean</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-96" start="3508" end="3514">Yes.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-97" start="3514" end="3521">No.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-98" start="3521" end="3531"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
penalty, because -- he said he&apos;s a very good listener and he cares about
don&apos;t know whether that is true or not.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-104" start="4048" end="4235">I know that he had done a lot
else who did <Event TYPE="Life" SUBTYPE="Die">it</Event>.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-105" start="4235" end="4453">I think given such as I have heard, even though like
don&apos;t quite see how he could not be guilty if they&apos;ve got so much that
appears to point to him.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-106" start="4453" end="4534">And what would be the motive for anybody
trying to -- to get him if it wasn&apos;t</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-107" start="4534" end="4544"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Mohammed</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-108" start="4544" end="4551">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
