<DOC>
<DOCID> fsh_29350 </DOCID>
<DOCTYPE SOURCE="telephone"> CONVERSATION </DOCTYPE>
<DATETIME> 20041206-18:15:01 </DATETIME>
<BODY>
<TEXT>
<TURN>
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Middle East</ENAMEX> peace process?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-8" start="440" end="446"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-9" start="446" end="472">I&apos;m <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX> from <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Indiana</ENAMEX>.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-10" start="472" end="479"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-11" start="479" end="518">Okay, I&apos;m <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX> from, um,  <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Atlanta</ENAMEX>.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-12" start="518" end="524"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-13" start="524" end="529">Hi.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-14" start="529" end="569">So, what do you think about -- <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Arafat</ENAMEX>?</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-15" start="569" end="584">Was he a h-</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-16" start="584" end="591"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-17" start="591" end="653">Uh, I think that, um,  I bet he wasn&apos;t a really good leader.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-18" start="653" end="905">I think
that, um,  that his situation -- -- well, see I got to the -- to- to the
level of power that he was in -- back in the eighties -- and once he, um,
you know, started getting wealthy and started getting known,  that
his agenda ch- uh, changed</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-19" start="905" end="911"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-20" start="911" end="919">Mhm.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-21" start="919" end="926"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-23" start="1061" end="1114">I really don&apos;t think that -- they wanted to coexist.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-24" start="1114" end="1228">I think that, um,
he wanted -- you know, all his people -- all his people wanted to
coexist with the -- Israelis.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-25" start="1228" end="1334">I think that, um,  his <Event TYPE="Life" SUBTYPE="Die">death</Event> -- marks a
don&apos;t think that in that area of the, um, world that you could
there&apos;s always going to be a <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">conflict</Event> there.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-28" start="1513" end="1664">Um,  I think that, uh,
the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">United States</ENAMEX> should open up -- their -- doors to -- not help, but
support any, um, process for peace in the area, though.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-29" start="1664" end="1835">I don&apos;t think
that we should get involved to a level, a point where we&apos;re <Event TYPE="Movement" SUBTYPE="Transport">sending</Event>
like that,  um.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-30" start="1835" end="1913">There&apos;s a lot of stuff that can be done -- by just
verbal suppo- -- you know.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-31" start="1913" end="1976">I think that now he&apos;s <Event TYPE="Life" SUBTYPE="Die">gone</Event>, his family is
still around, and</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-32" start="1976" end="1982"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-33" start="1982" end="1991">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-34" start="1991" end="1998"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
they -- if they bring people in that wasn&apos;t involved with his cabinet,
coexist.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-36" start="2353" end="2538">If they can find somebody like that, then I think that they
should f- support him and, um,  and back him up -- in trying to help
define -- peace in the area where peace is impossible.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-37" start="2538" end="2569">What do you
think about it?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-38" start="2569" end="2575"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-39" start="2575" end="2593">I agree with you.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-40" start="2593" end="2678">I didn&apos;t know that much about it, I wasn&apos;t much into
politics back in the eighties.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-41" start="2678" end="2846">I was more,  um,  kind of a -- I was a
kid on the run from abusive parents back then so that wasn&apos;t a,  you
know, one of my topics of interest at the time, it is now.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-42" start="2846" end="3078">Um,  I --
my roommate, and I still don&apos;t know that much about -- I&apos;d love to
know more about politics and I&apos;m trying to learn more,  uh, tells me,
you know, he was such a terrible man but, eh, I don&apos;t listen to
everything he says.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-43" start="3078" end="3214">And I think it -- -- I mean, it would be nice to
have peace over there, but I agree with you, I don&apos;t think it&apos;s ever
going to happen.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-44" start="3214" end="3288">I mean, not the way -- -- not the way they&apos;ll -- -- not
like it is here.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-45" start="3288" end="3342">And I agree that we shouldn&apos;t <Event TYPE="Movement" SUBTYPE="Transport">send</Event> people over
there.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-46" start="3342" end="3382">We&apos;ve got enough stuff going on with</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-47" start="3382" end="3389"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-48" start="3389" end="3398">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-49" start="3398" end="3404"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-50" start="3404" end="3463"><ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> and I- and, um,  the -- other -- -- the other guy.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-51" start="3463" end="3470"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-52" start="3470" end="3479">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-53" start="3479" end="3485"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
the that&apos;s</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-55" start="3568" end="3575"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-56" start="3575" end="3584">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-57" start="3584" end="3590"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-58" start="3590" end="3648">that would be just putting it over the edge right there.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-59" start="3648" end="3700">But I think
ought support, you know, a man that,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-60" start="3700" end="3707"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-61" start="3707" end="3715">Mhm.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-62" start="3715" end="3721"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
somebody that is</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-64" start="3806" end="3813"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-65" start="3813" end="3822">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-66" start="3822" end="3828"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-67" start="3828" end="3899">peaceful -- and, I don&apos;t know, I&apos;d like to learn more about the Bible.</sentence>
<sentence ID="SENT-68" start="3899" end="3948">My parents never took me to church or anything.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-69" start="3948" end="3960">But, um,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-70" start="3960" end="3967"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-71" start="3967" end="3976">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-72" start="3976" end="3982"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-73" start="3982" end="4111">I&apos;d like to -- I know that,  you know, there&apos;s been problems, a lot of
<Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">conflict</Event> over there, and it seems like no matter what,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-74" start="4111" end="4118"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Roger</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-75" start="4118" end="4125">Ah.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-76" start="4125" end="4131"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
no matter what.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
longer than the age that I am -- old, so, but I- I- I- I&apos;ve noticed -- on
terrorists in the area.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-80" start="5025" end="5089">But I don&apos;t think that he had the same image
to the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Gaza strip</ENAMEX>, and to re-take <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Jerusalem</ENAMEX> -- and other cities near
say, you know, we <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">conquered</Event> the Israelis.</sentence>  <sentence ID="SENT-82" start="5465" end="5661">It&apos;s a matter of, uh -- I
mean, it&apos;s more than just land,  it&apos;s a, um,  <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">conflict</Event> of- -- of,  um,
they don&apos;t like each other,</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-83" start="5661" end="5667"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Barb</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-84" start="5667" end="5674">Yeah.</sentence>
</TURN>
</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
