<DOC>
<DOCTYPE SOURCE="broadcast conversation"> STORY </DOCTYPE>
<DATETIME> 2003-05-04T12:00:00-05:00 </DATETIME> 
<BODY>
<HEADLINE>
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-1" start="187" end="196"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
</TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-4" start="330" end="350">(BEGIN VIDEOTAPE)</sentence>
<TURN>
open border, if you will.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-7" start="528" end="648">Has the situation improved, especially in the
aftermath now of the secretary of state&apos;s <Event TYPE="Contact" SUBTYPE="Meet">meeting</Event> with <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Bashar al-Asad</ENAMEX>?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-8" start="648" end="658"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
on the phone a bit, and it&apos;s not, I think you need to let the dust settle
on that.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-11" start="813" end="941">He&apos;s, in my judgment, had a visit that was worth doing, and the
president asked him to do it, and it was the right thing to do.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-12" start="941" end="972">We&apos;ll see
what progress comes.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-13" start="972" end="1027">You know, words are one thing, actions are another.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-14" start="1027" end="1036"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
to take?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-16" start="1191" end="1201"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-17" start="1201" end="1258">I know what they&apos;ve been doing, and it&apos;s been unhelpful.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-18" start="1258" end="1407">I know that
view, they were making some unwise decisions previously.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-20" start="1470" end="1526">What they&apos;ll do
after this visit remains to be seen.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-21" start="1526" end="1535"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-22" start="1535" end="1772">The secretary of state has written you a <Event TYPE="Contact" SUBTYPE="Phone-Write">letter</Event> expressing, apparently,
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Cuba</ENAMEX>, about 600 or so of them.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-23" start="1772" end="1851">Is there any movement in trying to
determine the fate of these individuals?</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-24" start="1851" end="1861"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-26" start="1930" end="1939"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-27" start="1939" end="1969">All right, tell me what...</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
figure out what law enforcement process might be appropriate, and what
<ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Colin</ENAMEX> and I have been concerned about, both of us, is that it&apos;s taking so
long.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-31" start="2415" end="2757">There are a number of countries, and the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Department of State</ENAMEX> has
the responsibility of dealing with those countries, that have foreign
nationals in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Gitmo</ENAMEX>, in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Guantanamo Bay</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Cuba</ENAMEX>, being detained, and those
countries, understandably, would like to know when they could have those
people.So the inter-agency process takes a great deal of time.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-32" start="2757" end="2843"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Colin</ENAMEX> and
I are trying to speed up that process, and that&apos;s what that&apos;s all about.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-33" start="2843" end="2852"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-34" start="2852" end="2925">Let me just, a couple of nuggets to sort of wrap up before I let you go.</sentence>
<sentence ID="SENT-35" start="2925" end="2957">Victory parades for the troops.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-36" start="2957" end="3063">I remember covering General <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Schwarzkopf</ENAMEX>,
the parades in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Washington</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">New York</ENAMEX> after the first <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Gulf</ENAMEX> War.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-37" start="3063" end="3188">Do you
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-38" start="3188" end="3198"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-39" start="3198" end="3347">There&apos;s no question but that the troops, the young men and women, did
such a superb job that there has to be a way to honor them, and there
will be.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-40" start="3347" end="3500">And General <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Franks</ENAMEX> and his team have done just a superb job for
our country and for the world, and indeed for the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraqi</ENAMEX> people, who have
been liberated.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-41" start="3500" end="3532">What&apos;s the best way to do that?</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-42" start="3532" end="3685">In the case of 1991, the
it was a very different task.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-44" start="3733" end="3824">It was to remove that regime, and it&apos;s part
of a global <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">war</Event> on <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">terrorism</Event> that is not over.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-45" start="3824" end="3970">We still have to face the
problem of a number of global terrorist networks and terrorist states
that exist, that work with those global networks.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-46" start="3970" end="4118">And on the one hand we
will, in fact, find a way to honor the courage and dedication and talent
of these young men and women, and we&apos;ll do it well.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-47" start="4118" end="4179">Whether it will be
modeled off the 1991 thing, I don&apos;t know.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-48" start="4179" end="4243">I kind of doubt it, because
it&apos;s such a different circumstance.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-49" start="4243" end="4299">Certainly, our <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">war</Event> plan was not
modeled off of 1991.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-50" start="4299" end="4308"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BLITZER</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-51" start="4308" end="4343">One final question on <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">North Korea</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-52" start="4343" end="4409">If the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">North Koreans</ENAMEX> pursue their
nuclear weapons ambitions...</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-53" start="4409" end="4419"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-54" start="4419" end="4427">Yes.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-57" start="4501" end="4511"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">RUMSFELD</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-58" start="4511" end="4562">I&apos;m not one who speculates about things like that.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-59" start="4562" end="4898">I know that back in
that was not appropriate.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-60" start="4898" end="4970">But those are very serious issues, and I leave
them for the president.</sentence>
</TURN>
</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
