<DOC>
<DATETIME> 2003-04-02T16:00:00-05:00 </DATETIME> 
<BODY>
<HEADLINE>
Push to Baghdad Begins; POW Safe in Army&apos;s Care
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
<TURN>
factor in the <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">fighting</Event> there.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-4" start="374" end="454">And to the south, <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">British</ENAMEX> forces continue
their <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">attack</Event> on targets around <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Basra</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-5" start="454" end="492"><ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">ITN</ENAMEX> correspondent <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Tim Ewart</ENAMEX>
reports.</sentence>
</TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-6" start="492" end="512">(BEGIN VIDEOTAPE)</sentence>
<TURN>
southwest of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Baghdad</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-9" start="632" end="704">They are facing <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Saddam Hussein</ENAMEX>&apos;s <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Republican Guard</ENAMEX>,
the regime right now and will remain pointed at it until the regime is
gone.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-17" start="1087" end="1094"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">EWART</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-18" start="1094" end="1149">To the south, more black smoke over the town of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Basra</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-19" start="1149" end="1269"><ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">British</ENAMEX> troops
they said housed <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraqi</ENAMEX> fighters.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-20" start="1269" end="1534">There is much fear here of the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Saddam</ENAMEX>
possible.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-21" start="1534" end="1551"><ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Basra</ENAMEX> will fall.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-22" start="1551" end="1623">But there may first be <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">fighting</Event> in the
capital, 250 miles to the north.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-23" start="1623" end="1660"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Tim Ewart</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">ITV News</ENAMEX>, southern <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Iraq</ENAMEX>.</sentence>
</TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-24" start="1660" end="1678">(END VIDEOTAPE)</sentence>
<TURN>
called a ferocious <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">bombardment</Event>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-27" start="1855" end="1904"><Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">It</Event> happened outside the oil-rich city of
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Kirkuk</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-28" start="1904" end="1934"><ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">CNN</ENAMEX>&apos;s <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Brent Sadler</ENAMEX> is there.</sentence>
</TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-29" start="1934" end="1954">(BEGIN VIDEOTAPE)</sentence>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-30" start="1954" end="1987"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">BRENT SADLER, CNN CORRESPONDENT</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
wealth.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-32" start="2063" end="2119">A road that&apos;s now in the hands of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraqi</ENAMEX> Kurdish forces.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-33" start="2119" end="2207">Occupying
onslaught of coalition <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">bombing</Event>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-36" start="2365" end="2444">This is the end of the road for Kurdish
forces manning this remote checkpoint.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-37" start="2444" end="2494">But with special permission, they
let us through.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-38" start="2494" end="2663">We are now between the lines, a no man&apos;s land of
easy artillery range of <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Saddam Hussein</ENAMEX>&apos;s forces and circling <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Kirkuk</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-40" start="2757" end="2887">The
oil field remain intact.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-42" start="2928" end="2981">Also intact, <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Kirkuk</ENAMEX>&apos;s defenses, in the distant
haze.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-43" start="2981" end="3090"><ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX>&apos;s armed opposition, including these Kurds, waits on the
sidelines to join the fray, if <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">America</ENAMEX> asks.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<SPEAKER> <sentence ID="SENT-44" start="3090" end="3144"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">PRIME MINISTER BARHAM SALEH, KURDISTAN REGIONAL GOV.</ENAMEX></sentence> </SPEAKER>
<sentence ID="SENT-45" start="3144" end="3176">This is about freedom for <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-46" start="3176" end="3305">This is about the liberation of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX>, and
we Iraqis must shoulder the responsibility of helping in the process of
liberation.</sentence>
</TURN>
<TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-48" start="3313" end="3366">And, says the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraqi</ENAMEX> opposition, in winning this <Event TYPE="Conflict" SUBTYPE="Attack">war</Event>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-49" start="3366" end="3416"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Brent Sadler</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">CNN</ENAMEX>,
near <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Kirkuk</ENAMEX> in northern Iraq.</sentence>
</TURN>
<sentence ID="SENT-50" start="3416" end="3432">(END VIDEOTAPE)</sentence>
</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
