<DOC>
<DOCID> APW_ENG_20030422.0485 </DOCID>
<DOCTYPE SOURCE="newswire"> NEWS STORY </DOCTYPE>
<DATETIME> 20030422 </DATETIME>
<BODY>
<HEADLINE>
U.S. won&apos;t choose subcontractors for rebuilding Iraq, U.S. official
says
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Tuesday that the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">U.S</ENAMEX>. government won&apos;t be involved in choosing
subcontractors for <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">American</ENAMEX> companies named to help rebuild <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX>.</sentence>

<sentence ID="SENT-3" start="345" end="460">``The way it works is that there have been an initial set of
contracts let to <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">US</ENAMEX> companies, since it&apos;s <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">U.S</ENAMEX>. money.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-4" start="460" end="543">Those companies
can subcontract to any company they want,&apos;&apos; <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Elizabeth Jones</ENAMEX> said.</sentence>


<sentence ID="SENT-6" start="649" end="761">``The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">U.S</ENAMEX>. government has done what it is going to do: it has opened
up the process to international companies.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-7" start="761" end="801">We can&apos;t direct
commerce,&apos;&apos; <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Jones</ENAMEX> said.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-8" start="801" end="897">``Once it&apos;s a commercial proposition, then
international bidding processes come into effect.&apos;&apos;</sentence>

Wednesday.</sentence>

<sentence ID="SENT-10" start="1044" end="1193">About 50 <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Portuguese</ENAMEX> companies - mostly in the construction sector  _ 
are applying for subcontracts to help rebuild <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Portuguese</ENAMEX> media

</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
