<DOC>
<DOCID> BACONSREBELLION_20050222.0817 </DOCID>
<DOCTYPE SOURCE="weblog"> WEB TEXT </DOCTYPE>
<DATETIME> 2005-02-22T08:17:00 </DATETIME>
<BODY>
<HEADLINE>
Two Reactions, Two Worlds
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
<POST>
<POSTER> <sentence ID="SENT-1" start="98" end="111"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Will Vehrs</ENAMEX></sentence> </POSTER>
<POSTDATE> <sentence ID="SENT-2" start="111" end="132">2005-02-22T08:17:00</sentence> </POSTDATE>
serve in the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">House of Delegates</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-5" start="231" end="309">There&apos;s a brief profile of <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Ebbin</ENAMEX> by
<ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Kristen Gelineau</ENAMEX> in today&apos;s Daily Press .</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-6" start="309" end="586">What I found interesting was
would ... talk about,&quot; said Del.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-7" start="586" end="618"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Ward Armstrong</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">D</ENAMEX>-<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Henry County</ENAMEX>.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-8" start="618" end="655">&quot;That
clearly has not been the case.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-9" start="655" end="690">He is a very versatile delegate.&quot;</sentence>

was the sponsor of the gay adoption bill, said he&apos;s not trying to stamp
<ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Loudoun</ENAMEX> Republican offered: &quot;He&apos;s always prompt and, you know, on time
to meetings.&quot;</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-13" start="1114" end="1165">A moment later, he added, &quot;I think he works hard.&quot;</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-14" start="1165" end="1297">I think
it&apos;s possible to support some of <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Black</ENAMEX>&apos;s positions but still be very
</POST>
<POST>
<POSTER> <sentence ID="SENT-15" start="1297" end="1304"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Paul</ENAMEX></sentence> </POSTER>
<POSTDATE> <sentence ID="SENT-16" start="1304" end="1325">????-??-??T11:16:00</sentence> </POSTDATE>
<sentence ID="SENT-17" start="1325" end="1355"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Dick Black</ENAMEX> is a statesman.</sentence>
</POST>
<POST>
<POSTER> <sentence ID="SENT-18" start="1355" end="1367"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Salt Lick</ENAMEX></sentence> </POSTER>
<POSTDATE> <sentence ID="SENT-19" start="1367" end="1388">????-??-??T14:33:00</sentence> </POSTDATE>
<sentence ID="SENT-20" start="1388" end="1427">Odd how different our perceptions are.</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-21" start="1427" end="1504">I read <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Black</ENAMEX>&apos;s comment as more
call me &quot;prompt&quot; and &quot;hard-working&quot; than &quot;very versatile.&quot;</sentence> <sentence ID="SENT-23" start="1587" end="1747">The latter
sounds like weasel words -- &quot;Well,&quot; <ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Johnnie</ENAMEX>&apos;s teacher said, &quot;he&apos;s not
versatile.&quot;</sentence>
</POST>
<POST>
<POSTER> <sentence ID="SENT-24" start="1747" end="1760"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Will Vehrs</ENAMEX></sentence> </POSTER>
<POSTDATE> <sentence ID="SENT-25" start="1760" end="1781">????-??-??T14:56:00</sentence> </POSTDATE>
<ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Black</ENAMEX> made that troubled me.</sentence>

<sentence ID="SENT-27" start="1876" end="1946">I appreciate your take on it; that&apos;s why I love this comment section.</sentence>
<sentence ID="SENT-28" start="1946" end="1972">I may be way off-base.</sentence>
</POST>
<POST>
<POSTER> <sentence ID="SENT-29" start="1972" end="1979"><ENAMEX TYPE="PER">Paul</ENAMEX></sentence> </POSTER>
</POST>
</TEXT>
</BODY>
</DOC>
